

#### **Contact**



[+353] 85 136 9889



samkingstonryan@hotmail.com



Limerick, Ireland



shorturl.at/aeCF5



shorturl.at/nqxyR

### Education

- 2<sup>nd</sup> Level –

2013 - 2019

**Leaving Certificate** 

All Higher Level

Mathematics	English
French	Irish
Physics	History
Applied	Business
Mathematics	Studies

- 3<sup>rd</sup> Level –

**BSc Computer Games** 

**Development** 

University of Limerick 2019 - Current

### Interests

Gaming

Writing

**Politics** 

Guitar

Charity

# Sam Kingston Ryan

# Computer Science Student

#### **Profile**

A creative, diligent coder with experience in Java, C++, PHP, SQL, and HTML. My priority is always to learn, grow, and lead those around me to do the same. In my two years of college, I always lead group assignments, keeping everyone interested and engaged.

### Experience

#### Website Developer

Baker Media, May - October 2020

Worked in PHP and SQL to create stock systems, fitting lists, customer facing portals, etc for Con Brouder Fitted Kitchens. Also developed WordPress sites for other clients.

Reference: Kenneth Baker, 0879777360, kenneth@bakermedia.ie

### **Delivery Driver**

Lily House, June 2020 - Present

Delivering Chinese food every Monday and Friday, sometimes covering other shifts. Developed my skills in Driving and Customer Service.

### **Conference and Banqueting Waiter**

Castletroy Park Hotel & Castle Oaks House Hotel, June 2018 – December 2019

Worked as a waiter for weddings, meetings, tour bus breakfasts. Trained for bar work, manual handling, food safety, and Covid safety.

## My Github Portfolio

https://github.com/MirrimDeTradon/portfolio/